<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Green Garbage App</string>
    <string name="green_garbage">Green Garbage</string>
    <string name="forward">Forward</string>
    <string name="cameraview">cameraView</string>
    <string name="left">Left</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="right">Right</string>
    <string name="backward">Backward</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="about">about</string>
    <string name="about_us">About us</string>
    <string name="_0_00km_h">0.00 km/h</string>

    <!--UN info string: -->
    <string name="UN">UNs Sustainable Development \nGoal 12</string>
    <string name="link">Read more: UNs SDGS - Goal 12</string>
    <string name="UN_link"><a href="https://sdgs.un.org/goals/goal12">Read more: UNs SDGS - Goal 12</a></string>
    <string name="UN2015">In 2015 all United Nations Member States joined together for sustainable development and future. In UNs Sustainable Development Goal 12 - Responsible consumption and production, it presents the global “material footprint”, and it increased by 70 \% from 2000 to 2017.</string>

    <string name="contact">Team members:\n\nAdrian Niklasson \ngusnikada@student.gu.se\n\nAgata Ciuchta \ngusciuag@student.gu.se\n\nAnna Törngren \ngusolsang@student.gu.se\n\nChristopher Andersson \ngusandchbh@student.gu.se\n\nFaiza Amjad \ngusamjfa@student.gu.se\n\nUmair Irshad \ngusirsum@student.gu.se</string>
    <string name="edu_game">With our educational game, we would like to raise awareness about waste pollution and the negative impact it has on the environment, but in a fun way.</string>
    <string name="proposal">For the project, we plan to create a game that raises awareness about high levels of waste in all sorts of environments where the user is manually controlling the car on an app. The vehicle can explore the area whilst clearing up objects that are waste and everything that is not waste will be left in simulation without change.</string>
    <string name="github">GitHub - Group 7</string>
    <string name="_0m">0 m</string>

    <!--Recycle info string: -->
    <string name="metal.tx">Turn in all metal packaging for recycling. This includes small packaging, like caps, lids, the foil on a crème fraiche container, and screw caps. Everything is important.\nFood tins, spray cans, tubes, caps, lids, and dry paint cans (scraped out and dry) are examples of metal packaging.\nTake your metal packaging to a recycling station. Addresses to the recycling stations can be found at FTI (Förpackningsinsamlingen). There, you can also see which packaging you can leave at which station, and when a recycling station is emptied and cleaned.\nIf there is a collection point for metal packaging near or at your property, you can dispose of it there. Many of the municipalities’ manned recycling centres also have collection containers for the recycling of packaging.\n\nMetal cans with leftover paint or solvent must be handed in as hazardous waste so they can be disposed of properly. Cans that are completely scraped out and dry can be placed in the container for metal packaging.\nMetal electrical and electronic products must be disposed of as e-waste; see e-waste.\nMetal items that are not packaging, such as holders from tea lights, pitch torches and grave candles as well as frying pans, cutlery and metal buckets, must be handed in at a recycling centre as bulky waste. Do not forget to remove the wick holder from the tea light cup; otherwise, the cup will be sorted out with iron and the aluminium will burn up in the smelter.\nReturnable cans should be taken back to a shop to receive the deposit back.</string>
    <string name="plastic.tx">All plastic packaging, both hard and soft, must be sent for recycling. \nExamples of plastic packaging include plastic carrier bags, plastic bags, plastic tubes, refill packs, plastic film and foil, inner bags in, for example, cereal packs, bottles, jars, small cans and buckets (jam, yoghurt), chip bags and styrofoam, including meat and fish trays. \nTake your plastic packaging to a recycling station. Addresses to the recycling stations can be found at FTI (Förpackningsinsamlingen). There, you can also see which packaging you can leave at which station, and when a recycling station is emptied and cleaned. \nIf there is a collection point for plastic packaging near or at your property, you can dispose of it there. Many of the municipalities’ manned recycling centres also have collection containers for the recycling of packaging. \nRemove caps and lids. Empty your bag of plastic packaging into the container so that they lie there loosely. This facilitates recycling. \n\nPlastic returnable bottles should be taken back to a shop to receive the deposit back. \nLarge plastic packaging that does not fit into the opening of the container must be taken to a municipal recycling centre. \nStorage boxes for e.g. CDs, video cassettes, board games, and plastic flower pots should be discarded as residual waste. \nItems that are not packaging – children’s sledges, laundry baskets, furniture, etc. – are discarded as plastic waste at your recycling centre if they have the fraction. If not, they are discarded as bulky waste. Check with the staff at your recycling centre. \n\nRemember that if the packaging has any leftover glue, paint, solvent or similar, it should be handed in as hazardous waste. The same applies to plastic electrical items.</string>
    <string name="glass.tx">Glass bottles and jars are disposed of as glass packaging. Sort and turn in coloured and clear glass packaging separately.\nTake your glass packaging to a recycling station. Addresses to the recycling stations can be found at FTI (Förpackningsinsamlingen). There, you can also see which packaging you can leave at which station, and when a recycling station is emptied and cleaned. If there is a collection point for glass packaging near or at your property, you can dispose of it there. Many of the municipalities’ manned recycling centres also have collection containers for the recycling of packaging.\nFor glass packaging to be recycled, it must not be mixed with other items. In other words, ceramics, porcelain, drinking glasses and other glass products that are not packaging must not be placed in the recycling container for glass packaging. They should be handed in as residual waste or bulky waste at the recycling centre.\nLight bulbs are collected together with e-waste.\nReturnable glass bottles should be taken back to a shop to receive the deposit back.\nColoured and clear glass packaging are put in different containers to make it possible to recycle them. Although the same vehicle collects packaging from several different containers, it has separate compartments for coloured and clear glass, and in some cases also for other types of packaging. The different types of packaging are kept separate throughout the recycling process.</string>
    <string name="paper.tx">Paper packaging can become new paper packaging, but only if you hand it in for recycling.\nExamples of paper packaging include pasta and cereal boxes, milk and juice cartons, sugar and flour bags, dog food bags, paper carrier bags, corrugated boxes from TVs, stereos, furniture, packing paper, etc.\nTake your paper packaging to a recycling station. Addresses to the recycling stations can be found at FTI (Förpackningsinsamlingen). There, you can also see which packaging you can leave at which station, and when a recycling station is emptied and cleaned.\nIf there is a collection point for paper packaging near or at your property, you can dispose of it there. Many of the municipalities’ manned recycling centres also have collection containers for the recycling of packaging.\nPlease remove plastic caps and dispose of them with plastic packaging. And remember that newspapers, catalogues and similar items should be placed in the container for newspapers and recyclable paper. Envelopes should be placed in the residual waste bin.</string>
    <string name="foodWaste.tx">In many places, food scraps and other food waste are collected separately. The energy can then be recovered and used for heating and fuel, while the nutrients are used to grow new food.\nDifferent rules apply to what should be sorted out, depending on how the food waste will be treated. Always use the special bags distributed to households for food waste. And make sure no plastic packaging or other foreign objects end up in these bags.\nIt is also possible to have a compost bin at home for food waste. Before starting to compost food waste, contact your municipality for more information and to register home composting.</string>
    <string name="sopor">Text from: sopor.nu</string>
</resources>